Do you realize that
four weeks from today
we're getting married?
Four weeks, baby!
Four weeks!
Do you realize that
you get louder each week?
There's still so much to do.
Hey, have you written
your vows yet?
I figured I'd just buy those.
"Pat, I'd like to buy a vow."
Sweety, you know
I have no sense of humor
when it comes
to the wedding.
Right.
So... have you
written yours yet?
No, but I know exactly
what I'm going to say.
Do you happen
to know exactly
what I'm going to say?
You know what?
Let's just do it
right now, okay?
It won't be hard.
Just say what's
in your heart.
CHANDLER:
Look at her go.
She must love me more
than I love her.
What's wrong with me?
Ooh, don't open that door.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
( exhales sharply )
"Monica, there are no words..."
There are no words.
This should not be this hard.
All right.
Uh, oh, hey
you've done
this before, Ross.
What did you say when
you made up your vows?
Well, with Carol, I promised
never to love another woman
until the day I die.
She made no such promise.
I am so pathetic.
Monica knows
what she wants to say.
You should've seen her writing
and writing and writing.
Monica, what?
What?
What is the emergency?
You have to help me.
I'm supposed
to be writing my vows
and all I have is this.
Well... I like
the pretty little drawing
of you in the wedding dress.
Thank you.
Yeah, except your breasts
look kind of small.
Those are my eyes.
Those are my breasts.
Oh, yeah! Okay.
Why don't you just start
with something simple
like, um... "Monica,
from the moment I met you
I knew I loved you."
Yeah, I'm not sure
I can do that.
Everyone,
this is Chandler.
Hi, I'm, uh, Ross's
little sister.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Um, maybe you
could start with
"Chandler, even though
we were friends
"there was a part of me
that always knew
I wanted more."
All right, there's
a nuclear holocaust.
I'm the last man
on Earth.
Would you go out with me?
Eh.
Ooh, are we allowed
to lie in the vows?
Or maybe you don't talk
about your feelings
back then.
Yeah.
Maybe you just say
something about, you know
all the things
that he's taught you.
Like...
Or all the things
you've taught him.
Mmm.
Now, everybody knows
the basic erogenous zones.
You got one, two, three...
four...
five...
six and seven.
There are seven?
That's one?
( chuckling )
Kind of an important one.
Oh, you know...
You know what?
I was looking at
it upside down.
( laughs )
Well, you know,
sometimes that helps.
Okay, now
start out with
a-a little one...
A two...
A one, two, three...
A three...
A five...
A four...
A three, two...
Two...
A two, four, six...
Two, four, six...
Four...
Two...
Four, seven...
Five, seven...
Six, seven...
Seven...
Seven, seven,
seven...
Seven, seven, seven...
Seven!
Oh! I got it.
How about saying
something like
"Monica...
when I look back over
our time together..."
Yeah?
I can't do everything.
Look back over
your time together.
Oh, look, twins.
No fair.
I don't even have one.
How come they get two?
You'll get one.
Oh, yeah? When?
All right,
I'll tell you what.
When we're 40,
if neither of us are married
what do you say you and I
get together and have one?
Why won't I be married
when I'm 40?
Oh, no, no. No.
I-I just meant hypothetically.
Okay. Hypothetically, why won't
I be married when I'm 40?
No. No, no.
No, what is it?
Seriously, is there something
fundamentally unmarriable
about me?
Uh... uh...
Well?
Dear God, this parachute
is a knapsack.
I'm getting
married today!
Wahoo!
Do you think
he knew I was here?
Nice try.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look, Monica...
Look!
This is not going to work.
I bet this'll work.
( chuckling )
You are so great.
I love you.
What?
Nothing.
I said, I said "you're so great"
and then I just,
I just stopped talking.
You said you loved me.
I can't believe this.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
You love me!
No, I don't.
Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it.
( screams )
You know, I was thinking,
what if I, uh... unpack here?
Then all your stuff
would be here.
Well....
What if all my stuff was here?
Then you'd be going back
and forth all the time.
I mean... doesn't
make any sense.
Okay.
What if we live together and you
understand what I'm saying.
You wanted it to be a surprise.
Oh, my God.
Chandler... in all my life
I never thought
I would be so lucky...
as to fall in love
with my best... my best...
There's a reason why
girls don't do this.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll do it.
I thought...
( stammering ):
I-I can do this.
I thought that it mattered
what I said
or where I said it.
Then I realized
the only thing that matters
is that you...
you make me happier than
I ever thought I could be.
And if you let me
I will spend
the rest of my life
trying to make you
feel the same way.
Monica...?
Yeah?
Will you marry me?
Yes.
JOEY:
Can we come in yet?
We're dying out here.
Come in! Come in!
We're engaged!
( all cheering )
Hey.
Hi. What've you
guys been up to?
Oh, we were helping Chandler
write his vows
but he kicked us out
because Joey kept making
inappropriate suggestions.
How is "Monica, I love your
sweet ass" inappropriate?
How's Monica coming along
with her vows?
Let's just say it's lucky
she's got a sweet ass
'cause she's not so good
at the writing.
I can't believe in four weeks
they're going to be married.
Well, let's just hope
it works.
You know, nine out of ten
marriages end in divorce.
Phoebe, that's not true.
Yeah, you're right.
How's the missus?
I can't believe
they've been together
for three years.
Has it been that long?
Maybe it seems like less because
they hid it from us for so long.
( knocking )
JOEY:
Hey, it's me. I'm coming in.
( takes deep breath )
( bubbling )
I've had a very long, hard day.
I'm going to go
get some chicken.
You want some?
Uh, no thanks. No chicken.
Bye-bye, then.
( gasping )
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
He wouldn't leave.
He kept asking me
if I wanted chicken.
Chicken?
I could eat some chicken.
Hey, Joe!
Yeah, could I get a three-piece
some coleslaw and some beans
and a coke.
Ah-ah-ah-ah! Diet coke.
I don't know why they
didn't just tell us.
I know. It's not like
we weren't cool about it.
You... and-and you?
Yes, but you cannot
tell anyone.
No one knows.
How? When?
It happened in London.
In London?!
( stammers )
The reason we didn't tell anyone
was because we didn't want
to make a big deal out of it.
But it is a big deal.
I have to tell someone.
No, no, no, no.
You can't.
Please, please.
We just don't
want to deal
with telling
everyone, okay?
Just promise
you won't tell.
All right.
MONICA ( on phone ):
I can't wait to be with you.
I'll just tell Rachel
I'm going to be doing laundry
for a couple hours.
CHANDLER ( on phone):
Laundry, huh, is that
my new nickname?
MONICA:
Ah, you know what your nickname
is, Mr. Big...
( screams )
Oh, look.
There's Monica and Chandler.
Hey!
Hey, you guys! Hey!
Oh!
Aah! Aah!
What?
Aah! Chandler and Monica!
Chandler and Monica!
Oh, my God.
Aah! Chandler and Monica!
Oh, my God!
Aah! Oh, my eyes!
My eyes!
Oh, Phoebe, Phoebe.
Oh!
Okay, it's okay!
It's okay!
No, they're doing it!
I know.
They're doing...
I know. I know.
You know?!
Yes, I know
and Joey knows,
but Ross doesn't know
so you have to
stop screaming!
Hey, what's going on?
( screaming )
What? What?
Hi! Nothing.
Oh, God, we were just so excited
that you might get
this apartment.
Actually, it looks really good.
It looks pretty good!
Get in here!
Come on!
( all screaming and cheering)
Okay, so now
they know you know
and they don't know
that Rachel knows?
Yes.
But you know what?
It doesn't matter
who knows what.
Now enough of us know
that we can just
tell them we know.
Now all the lying
and the secrets
will finally be over.
Or we could not
tell them we know
and have a little fun
of our own.
All right, honey,
we better go
if we're going
to catch that movie.
( all saying "bye" )
Bye, Chandler.
I miss you already.
Okay, did you see that
with the inappropriate--
and the pinching?
Actually, I did.
Okay, so now
do you believe
that she's
attracted to me?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, she knows about us.
Phoebe knows about us.
Well, I didn't tell them.
Them?
Who's them?
Uh... Phoebe... and Joey.
Joey?
And Rachel.
I would've told you
but they made me promise
not to tell.
Oh, man, they think
they are so slick
messing with us.
But see, they
don't know
that we know
that they know.
So...
Ah, yes...
the messers become the messies.
Oh, my God, he wants me
to come over
and feel his bicep and more.
Are you kidding?
No.
I cannot believe
he would do that to Mon...
W...
Joey, do they know that we know?
No.
Joey?
They know you know.
Oh, I knew it!
Oh, I cannot
believe those two.
They thought that they
could mess with us?
They're trying
to mess with us?
Oh...
They don't know that we
know they know we know.
Oh...
And, Joey, you
can't say anything.
Couldn't if I wanted to.
Listen, this is totally
getting out of hand, okay?
She wants me to put
lotion on her.
She's bluffing.
Look, she's not
backing down.
She went like this...
H-He's not backing down.
He went to get lotion.
( door opens )
Oh, man, aren't you
guys done yet?
Joey, look, just look
at it this way--
the sooner Phoebe
breaks Chandler
the sooner this is all
over and out in the open.
Ooh, I like that.
Oh, okay...
show him your bra.
He's afraid of bras--
can't work them.
Joey!
Wow, you didn't rip off
any buttons.
It's not my first time.
You go back out there
and you seduce her
till she cracks.
Okay, give me a second.
Did you clean
up in here?
Of course.
Oh, you're going.
Um, not without you, lover.
So... this is my bra.
It's very, very nice.
Well, come here.
I'm very happy we're going
to have all the sex.
You should be.
I'm very bendy.
I'm going to
kiss you now.
Not if I kiss you first.
Well, I guess there's
nothing left
for us to do but...
but kiss.
Here it comes.
Our first kiss.
Okay, okay, okay,
okay, fine, you win!
I can't have sex with you.
And why not?
Because I'm in love with Monica.
You're... you're what?
Love her.
That's right.
I... love... her.
I love you, Monica.
I love you,
too, Chandler.
I just... I thought you
guys were doing it.
I didn't know
you were in love.
So that's it.
It's over.
Everybody knows.
Well, actually,
Ross doesn't.
Yes, and we'd appreciate it
if no one told him yet.
No.
Wha-Wha...
What are you doing?!
Get off my sister!
You know, your friends
getting married
it's got to change things.
You really think
it'll be that different?
How could it not be?
I mean, pretty soon they're
going to be having kids
and then they're just going
to be hanging out
with other couples
who have kids
and then maybe they're going
to have to leave the city
to be near a Volvo dealership.
Well... things change.
But I don't want them
to move to a
Volvo dealership.
It'll be okay, Joe.
Sorry. I just...
I like things
the way they are.
Hey, who's this
little naked guy?
Uh, that little naked guy
would be me.
Ah, ha, look at
the little thing.
Yes.
Yes, fine,
that is my penis.
Can we be grownups now?
Who are those people?
Got me.
Oh, that's Nana right there
in the middle.
Wow.
Yeah, let's see.
"Me and the gang at Java Joe's."
Wow, Monica, you look
just like your grandmother.
How old was she there?
Let's see... "1939."
Uh, 24, 25.
Yeah.
Huh.
Looks like a fun gang.
Ooh, look, look,
look, look, look...
I got Monica naked.
Let me see.
No, no, that
would be me again.
Hey, you guys.
Hey.
What's going on?
Well, we were just talking
about you guys getting married
and how great it is.
Yeah, you could get a Volvo.
If that's what you really want.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Hmm.
So, we both finished
our vows.
Oh, can we read them?
As long as I don't
hear Chandler's
and he doesn't hear mine.
Okay.
Oh...
( laughing )
Oh, that's beautiful.
Funny one.
That's a good one.
Monica, will
you marry me?
( laughing )
What? I don't get it.
Oh...
( laughing )
Oh, man, this
is hilarious.
Chandler!
Don't worry, honey,
we'll make yours funnier.
Okay. What do
you guys think?
Dude...
I have never known
love like this.
You really like it?
Dude...
How-how did you
write this?
I stole Monica's
and changed the name. Shh.
You can't do that.
If he goes first,
he can.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]